urbanterror.net 2011-11-24

# Urban Terror Support : Licences : Privacy Policy

##  Licences

## Privacy Policy

### Urban Terror Accounts Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting www.urbanterror.info. We, Frozen Sand LLC, as owner of the game Urban Terror™ and Urban Terror Accounts, appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the Internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information and whether we disclose that information to anyone.

#### Cookies

Cookies are small files containing information that enables our website to authenticate you. To be able to make use of our services you need to allow Frozen Sand and its third party partners the use of cookies.

#### What Information We Collect and How We Use It

Any information we, Frozen Sand, collect on our Site generally falls into the Personally Identifiable Information category. Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that lets us know specifically who you are. In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. On occasion, other information such as IP addresses may be used to block certain individuals from accessing our site or player tracking. By using any Urban Terror Accounts service or website, you agree to allowing the use of this information, if necessary, for both internal and public banlist purposes. 

Frozen Sand also collects information from participating game servers. This information is collected and recorded for Player tracking. Typically this type of information includes Player Names and IP Addresses. By registering or using an account, you agree to the collection of this information for the above purposes. 

#### Sharing your information

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be used for your purchases and retained in hard copy form of the original invoice as well as within our database system, which generates our invoices.

From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Limited Warranty or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves. 

#### Links to other websites

Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional information or services. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

#### Changes to this statement

Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed.

By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use.

#### Contact Us

If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to privacy[*at*]urbanterror.info. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.

 **Frozen Sand Team**

 _This Privacy Statement was last revised on June 21, 2009._

_by - By FS ~SG~ [Kalish](http://www.urbanterror.info/members/profile/kalish/)  -  Wednesday, 23 December 2009  -  viewed by 14 members and 1067 visitors_
